Guide to the Max S. Baucus Papers 1958-2016 (bulk 1974-2014)
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Photographs, 1958-2014; Series XIII; 29.6 linear feet; 281.9 gigabytes
  - Photographs, 1959-2013; Sub-series 1; 25.7 linear feet
    - 1985 0711 DC MM Nancy Forbes of MT Food Bank Board of Great Falls, July 11, 1985; Max Baucus with director of Montana Food Bank Board Nancy L. Forbes of Great Falls, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/44)
    - 1985 0905 DC MM Marie and Gerald Deline of Bozeman, September 5, 1985; Max Baucus with Marie and Gerald Deline of Bozeman, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/45)
    - 1985 0911 DC MM Jim and Marcee Allen of Bozeman, September 11, 1985; Max Baucus with Jim and Marcee Allen of Bozeman, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/46)
    - 1985 0912 DC MM MT Pork Producers, September 12, 1985; Max Baucus with Montana Pork Producers members First Vice President Duane Braaten of Kalispell, Montana; President Dewey Schmitt of Three Forks, Montana; Executive Secretary Sue Huls of Bozeman, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/47)
    - 1985 0912 DC Nike Capital Challenge, September 12, 1985; Max Baucus running in Nike Capital Challenge, with Olympic runner Joan Benoit, and with team members Jerry Solomon, Joan Flink, Sue Irving, and Bob Fitzgerald. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/48)
    - 1985 0914 MT Missoula Japanese Diet Tour at Louisiana Pacific Facility, September 14, 1985; Max Baucus on Japanese Diet Tour at Louisiana Pacific Facility. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/49)
    - 1985 0917 DC MM Future Farmers of America FFA, September 17, 1985; Max Baucus with state winner of the Future Farmers of America FFA National Community Development Project Bob Syvrud of Polson, Montana and state winner of the FFA National Community Development Project Dusty Sturm of Polson. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/50)
    - 1985 0925 DC MM J. Harry Johnson and Frank Daniels of Sidney, September 25, 1985; Max Baucus with farmers J. Harry Johnson and Frank Daniels, both of Sidney, Montana and ASCS Business and Farming. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/51)
    - 1985 0926 DC MM USTR Nominee Alan Woods, September 26, 1985; Max Baucus with nominee for deputy USTR Alan Woods of Washington, D.C. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/52)
    - 1985 0926 DC MM Edward Cotter of Ireland, September 26, 1985; Max Baucus with Mike Mansfield's relative Edward Cotter of Ireland. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/53)
    - 1985 1001 DC MM Matt and Karla Knox of Winifred, October 1, 1985; Max Baucus with Matt and Karla Knox of Winifred, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/54)
    - 1985 1002 DC MM Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, October 2, 1985; Max Baucus with Carl J. Knutson, Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees railroad union member.. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/55)
    - 1985 1002 DC MM Canadian Ambassador Allan Gotlieb, October 2, 1985; Max Baucus with Ambassador Allan Gotlieb of Canada. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/56)
    - 1985 1003 DC MM MT Housing Board, October 3, 1985; Max Baucus with Montana Housing Board members John Buchanan of Great Falls; Jay McLeod of Helena; Bill Groff of Victor; Linda Forrey of Townsend. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/57)
    - 1985 1003 DC MM Shawn Burland of Maryland, October 3, 1985; Max Baucus with Shawn Burland of Maryland. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/58)
    - 1985 1007 DC MSB with Family, October 7, 1985; Max Baucus with his family and family friends, Jack and Rhoda Stephenson, Jr. of Great Falls, Montana; John and Jean Baucus of Helena, Montana; Will and Jean Baucus of Great Falls. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/59)
    - 1985 1007 DC MM Region 8 Minority Small Business Person of the Year, October 7, 1985; Max Baucus with Region 8 Minority Small Business Person of the Year, owner of Joe's Smoke Ring, Dorothy Clickenbeard with Larry Clickenbeard, both of Arlee, Montana and Jackie McRae of Georgia. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/60)
    - 1985 1008 DC MM Nedrud Family of Missoula, October 8, 1985; Max Baucus with the Nedrud family of Missoula, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/61)
    - 1985 1008 DC MM Pete and Helen Brown of Billings, October 8, 1985; Max Baucus with Willis T. "Pete" and Helen Brown of Billings, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/62)
    - 1985 1009 DC MM Elliott and Winifred Robocker of Kalispell, October 9, 1985; Max Baucus with director of the Flathead REA Elliott and Winifred Robocker of Kalispell, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/63)
    - 1985 1010 DC MM Former Staff EA Mike Cooney and Dee Ann Cooney, October 10, 1985; Max Baucus with former executive assistant Mike Cooney and Dee Ann Cooney. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/64)
    - 1985 1016 DC MM Journal of International Studies, October 16, 1985; Max Baucus with Journal of International Studies members, Editor in Chief Ma Yaohui and researcher Xie Xiaochuan, both of Beijing, China and interpreter Philip Haung. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/65)
    - 1985 1016 DC MM Page Tim Warner of Bozeman, October 16, 1985; Max Baucus with Senate Democratic Page Tim Warner, Jr. of Bozeman, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/66)
    - 1985 1018 DC MM Foster Grandparent Program 50th Anniversary, October 18, 1985; Max Baucus with Foster Grandparent members celebrating 20th anniversary, Lura "Betty" Bellwood and Lila Itami, both of Great Falls, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/67)
    - 1985 1622 DC MM Federal Energy Efficiency Award Winners, October 22, 1985; Max Baucus with 1985 Federal Energy Efficiency award winners vice commander of the Malmstrom Air Force Base Colonel Bruce Harger of Great Falls, Montana; dep. Base civil engineer of Malmstrom Air Force Base Bob Moretti of Great Falls; possibly Eric Rasmussen of Congressional Affairs Energy Department. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/68)
    - 1985 1023 DC MM Bill and Nancy Chalgren of Libby, October 23, 1985; Max Baucus with Bill and Nancy Chalgren of Libby, Montana, one is a high school math teacher receiving the Presidential Award for Excellence in Math. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/69)
    - 1985 1023 DC MM Ken and Brenda Price of Helena, October 23, 1985; Max Baucus with high school science teacher and recipient of the Presidential Award for Excellence in Science, Ken Price and Brenda Price of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/70)
    - 1985 1023 DC Testifying at Senate Banking Subcommittee Hearing, October 23, 1985; Max Baucus sitting and testifying at Banking Subcommittee on International Finance and Monetary Policy hearing about exchange rates, constituents in background. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/71)
    - 1985 1025 DC MM FBI Academy Course Attendees, October 25, 1985; Max Baucus with FBI Academy Course attendees Sheriff Wade VanGilder of Superior, Montana; Jim Doxtater of Thompson Falls, Montana; Daniel L. Magone of Missoula, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/72)
    - 1985 1028 DC MM Jack Bauska and William Schneider, Jr., October 28, 1985; Max Baucus with Jack Bauska and William Schneider, Jr.. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/73)
    - 1985 1029 DC MM Satellite Earth Station Industry, October 29, 1985; Max Baucus with Valerie Hansen of Billings, M; Bill and Debi Burton of Bigfork, Montana, all of Satellite Earth Station Industry. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/74)
    - 1985 1030 DC MM Mountain Bell, October 30, 1985; Max Baucus with Mountain Bell outgoing President Jack Buckley and incoming President Jim Hughes, both of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/75)
    - 1985 1030 DC MM Steve and Donna Benedict of Missoula, Charles from Polson, October 30, 1985; Max Baucus with President of Missoula Chamber of Commerce Steve Benedict of KGRZ Radio and Donna Benedict, both of Missoula, Montana and Donna's father Charles of Polson, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/76)
    - 1985 1031 DC MM National Mental Health Conference Attendees, October 31, 1985; Max Baucus with National Mental Health Conference attendees Timothy Tate of Bozeman, Montana; Jaye Winegardner of Billings, Montana; Joan-Nell Mcfadden of Great Falls, Montana; Bonnie Hyatt-Murphy of Livingston, Montana; Ken and Char Messmore of Great Falls; David O. Armstrong of Billings. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/77)
    - 1985 1104 DC MM MT Association of Students MSU, November 4, 1985; Max Baucus with chairman of Associated Students of Montana State University ASMSU Michael Mortier of Bozeman, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/78)
    - 1985 1104 DC MM Sean Scott of Associated Students of MSU, November 4, 1985; Max Baucus with Associated Students of Montana State University ASMSU member Sean Scott of Bozeman, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/79)
    - 1985 1107 DC MM Akemi Dena Translator Works at Motorola DC, November 7, 1985; Max Baucus with assistant Vice President of Japanese operations for Motorola Akemi Denda of Washington, D.C. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/80)
    - 1985 1112 DC MM Leaders at UM and MSU College of Agriculture, November 12, 1985; Max Baucus with President Neil Bucklew of the University of Montana UM in Missoula, Montana and Dean Jim Welsh of the Montana State University College of Agriculture in Bozeman, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/81)
    - 1985 1204 DC MM Honey Stakeholders, December 4, 1985; Max Baucus with Honey Stakeholders Robert "Bob" Barnes of the Beaverhead Honey Company and of Dillon, Montana and Garry Rodenberg of Sioux Honey Association and of Wolf Point, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/82)
    - 1985 1205 D.C. MM Mansfield Foundation, December 5, 1985; Max Baucus with incoming President of the Mansfield Foundation David Steinberg. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/83)
    - 1985 1209 DC MM Edwin Stickney of MT Medical Association, December 9, 1985; Max Baucus with Dr. Edwin Stickney of the Montana Medical Association. (Box-folder Series 13 - 19/84)
    - 1985 1211 DC MM MT Medical Association, December 11, 1985; Max Baucus with Montana Medical Association doctors attending the NMA Conference, Dr. Paul and Jean Crellin of Billings, Montana; Dr. Jack Allaire of Great Falls, Montana; Dr. Van Kirke and Helen Nelson of Kalispell, Montana; Dr. Mike and Mary Sadaj of Butte, Montana; Dr. Brian and Diana Zins of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/1)
    - 1985 1212 DC MM Chase Hibbard, December 12, 1985; Max Baucus with his cousin Chase Hibbard, appointed to the Montana Alliance to Study Acid Rain by Governor Ted Schwinden. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/2)
    - 1985 1213 DC MM Joe Quilici of Butte and J.D. Lynch of Butte, December 13, 1985; Max Baucus with Montana Representative Joe Quilici and Montana Senator J.D. Lynch, both of Butte, Montana, attending National Conference of State Legislators. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/3)
    - 1985 1218 DC MM Bob Hoyer of Maryland, December 18, 1985; Max Baucus with Finance Committee Minority Health Professional staff member Bob Hoyer of Maryland. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/4)
    - 1985 1218 DC MM Former Staff LD Susan Irving, December 18, 1985; Max Baucus with Legislative Director Susan Irving. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/5)
    - 1986 0108 Unknown Korean First Secretary Chul-Kyoon Chang, January 8, 1986; Max Baucus with first secretary of the Korean Chul-Kyoon Chang during Danforth trip. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/6)
    - 1986 0108-0110 Japan and South Korea Trip, January 8-10, 1986; Photo album of Senator Danforth CODEL to Japan and South Korea. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/7)
    - 1986 01 Unknown News Conference, January 1986; Max Baucus with group of constituents attending a news conference. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/8)
    - 1986 01 Unknown Secretary of Air Force Russell Rourke and Wife Judy, January 1986; Max Baucus with secretary of the Air Force Russel Rourke and wife Judy of Maryland. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/9)
    - 1985 0603 DC MM MT Association of Health, June 3, 1985; Max Baucus with President of Montana Association of Health Cissy Filcher of Stevensville, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/10)
    - 1986 0110 Unknown Seoul News Conference, January 10, 1986; Max Baucus at Seoul news conference with constituents and speaking at podium. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/11)
    - 1986 0122-0123 NE Omaha Offutt Air Force Base, January 22-23, 1986; Max Baucus at Offutt Air Force Base in Omaha, NB with Montana Governor Ted Schwinden and commander in chief of Strategic Air Command General Larry D. Welch. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/12)
    - 1986 0128 DC MM MT School Board Association, January 28, 1986; Max Baucus with Montana School Board Association members President Karen Doolen of Billings, Montana; Wayne Buchanan of Helena, Montana; Vice President Robert Moodry of Butte, Montana; Executive Director Alice Tully of Missoula, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/13)
    - 1986 0129 MT Columbia Falls BPA Public Hearing, January 29, 1986; Max Baucus at public hearing in Columbia Falls, Montana gymnasium, and close up speaking. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/14)
    - 1986 0204 DC MM Bill and Colleen Shields of Great Falls, February 4, 1986; Max Baucus with Dr. Bill Shields and daughter Colleen Shields of Great Falls, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/15)
    - 1986 0204 DC MM MSU Small Business Institute Program, February 4, 1986; Max Baucus with Small Business Institute Program of Montana State University Business School Dick Dailey. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/16)
    - 1986 0206 DC MM Dave Shaenen of Billings, February 6, 1985; Max Baucus with Wesco Resources, Inc. consultant Dave Schaenen of Billings, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/17)
    - 1986 0206 DC MM Foreign Affairs Assembly of Korea Chairman Duwan Pong, February 6, 1986; Max Baucus with chairman of Foreign Affairs Committee of the National Assembly of Korea Duwan Pong. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/18)
    - 1986 0206 DC MM Loren Bough of Highwood and Paul Lincoln of Great Falls, February 6, 1986; Max Baucus with U.S. Senate Youth Scholarship scroll recipients Loren Bough of Highwood, Montana and Paul Lincoln of Great Falls, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/19)
    - 1986 0218 DC MM Darrell Winter of Billings, February 18, 1986; Max Baucus with Eastern Montana College student attending Campus Activity Convention Darrell Winter of Billings, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/20)
    - 1986 0219 DC MM Dottie Maitland of Kalispell, February 19, 1986; Max Baucus with President of Montana Leisure, Inc. Dottie Maitland of Kalispell, Montana, named "tour operator of the year". (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/21)
    - 1986 0220 DC MSB Named Activist on Trade, February 20, 1986; Max Baucus with Richard and Mrs. Whalen of WIRES, Ltd, Baucus named one of the Senate's activists on trade. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/22)
    - 1986 0225 DC MM American Legion Auxiliary, February 25, 1986; Max Baucus with American Legion Auxiliary members Barbara McDonough of Wolf Creek, Montana; Else Daniels of Scobey, Montana; Bette Kelley of Lakeside, Montana; Legion member Own Grinde of Whitefish, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/23)
    - 1986 0304 DC MM Howard Schwartz of Missoula, March 4, 1986; Max Baucus with city commissioner Howard Schwartz of Missoula, Montana on Indian taxation of reservation lands and funding for new jail. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/24)
    - 1986 0304 DC MM Janet Stevens of Missoula, March 4, 1986; Max Baucus with city commissioner Janet Stevens of Missoula on Indian taxation of reservation lands and funding for new jail. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/25)
    - 1986 0304 DC MM Longfellow Family of Helena, March 4, 1986; Max Baucus with Larry, Marlene, Tobi, and Duane LongFellow of Helena, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/26)
    - 1986 0306 DC MM National Association of Community Health Centers, March 6, 1986; Max Baucus with National Association of Community Health Centers members Allen Strange of Butte, Montana and Lil Anderson of Billings, Montana discussing public health programs and Medicare. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/27)
    - 1986 0306 DC MM National Association of Retired Federal Employees, March 6, 1986; Max Baucus with National Association of Retired Federal Employees members Leroy Keilman of Billings, Montana and Clara Sipe of Lolo, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/28)
    - 1986 0307 DC MM Joe Rizza of Helena, March 7, 1986; Max Baucus with director of Laboratories of St. Peter's Hospital Dr. Joe Rizza. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/29)
    - 1986 0307 DC MM Mary Gereau from Melcher Office, March 7, 1986; Max Baucus with Melcher Office retiree Mary Gereau. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/30)
    - 1986 0307 DC MM Phillis and John Moore of Kalispell, March 7, 1986; Max Baucus with DNC meeting attendees Phillis and John Moore, one is former President of MSDWC. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/31)
    - 1986 0310 DC MM Blue Mountain Women's Clinic, March 10, 1986; Max Baucus with Blue Mountain Women's Clinic Director Sally Mullen discussing pro-choice issues. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/32)
    - 1986 0310 DC MM Budweiser Distributor Bill Watkins of Missoula, March 10, 1986; Max Baucus with Budweiser beer distributor Bill Watkins discussing beer industry taxation. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/33)
    - 1986 0312 DC MM MT Office of Public Instruction OPI, March 12, 1986; Max Baucus with Lynn Havens of Kalispell, Montana and Ron Lukenbill of Helena, Montana from the Office of Public Instruction OPI, explaining learning strategy program and looking for funding. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/34)
    - 1986 0328 DC MM Eric Molvar of Missoula, March 28, 1986; Max Baucus with University of Montana UM Phi Gamma Delta Fraternity member Eric Molvar, wants Baucus to sponsor fraternity bike relay to benefit MADD. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/35)
    - 1986 0328 DC Pointing at Scythe on Wall, March 28, 1986; Max Baucus in office pointing to scythe mounted on the wall. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/36)
    - 1986 0328 DC Pointing at Scythe on Wall and 1986 0328 DC MM Eric Molvar of Missoula, March 28, 1986; Max Baucus in office pointing to scythe mounted on the wall and with University of Montana UM Phi Gamma Delta Fraternity member Eric Molvar contact sheets. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/37)
    - 1986 0408 DC MM Library Stakeholders, April 8, 1986; Max Baucus with library stakeholders C.E. "Abe" Abramson and daughter Ingrid of Missoula, Montana; Henry McClernan of Butte, Montana; Sara Parker of Helena, Montana; Deb Schlesinger of Helena; G. Patricia Abramson of New York, discussing library services and construction act, Gramm Rudman, revenue sharing. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/38)
    - 1986 0410 DC MM American Association of Homes for the Aging, April 10, 1986; Max Baucus with members of American Association of Homes for the Aging Don Peterson of Billings, Montana and of St. Johns Lutheran Home for the Aging and Joyce Anderson of Missoula, Montana and of Manor Home, discussing Medicaid and Medicare budget cuts and federal housing programs and nursing homes. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/39)
    - 1986 0411 DC MM Alice Long and Former Staff Press Secretary Carole Long, April 11, 1986; Max Baucus with Alice Long of California and former staff press secretary Carole Long. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/40)
    - 1986 0415 DC MM National Soft Drinks Association, April 15, 1986; Max Baucus with National Soft Drinks Association members Jim and Fran Wylder and Russ and Ruth Royter, all of Great Falls, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/41)
    - 1986 0416 DC MM MT Stockgrowers Association, April 16, 1986; Max Baucus with Montana Stockgrowers Association members Stuart Dogget of Helena, Montana and Charles Hahnkamp of Melrose, Montana, discussing noxious weeds and funding. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/42)
    - 1986 0421 DC MM Members of Coast Guard, April 21, 1986; Max Baucus with U.S. Coast Guard members Rumery and New. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/43)
    - 1986 0422 DC MM Larry Obie of Havre, April 22, 1986; Max Baucus with optometrist Larry Obie of Havre, Montana discussing vision care and Medicare problems. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/44)
    - 1986 0428 DC MM Tom Asay of Forsythe, April 28, 1986; Max Baucus with State Representative Tom Asay of Forsythe, discussing farm and agriculture issues. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/45)
    - Unknown DC Military Event at Arlington National Cemetery, April 1986; Max Baucus at military event at Arlington National Cemetery. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/46-49)
    - 1986 0501 DC MM Hugh and Cassandra Spain of Belgrade, May 1, 1986; Max Baucus with Hugh and Cassandra Spain of Belgrade, Montana, inviting Baucus to Belgrade Centennial. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/50)
    - 1986 0501 DC Press Conference RE Reducing Trade Barriers, May 1, 1986; Max Baucus at press conference concerning trade barrier reduction with 10 other Democrats, including Robert Strauss, in LBJ Room in the Capitol Building at Tokyo Summit. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/51)
    - 1986 0507 DC MM Dick Reid of Inland Forest Resource Council of Missoula, May 7, 1986; Max Baucus with Vice President Dick Reid of the Inland Forest Resource Council of Missoula, Montana discussing Canadian Timber and forest industry problems. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/52)
    - 1986 0515 DC MM Robert Wynia of Great Falls, May 15, 1986; Max Baucus with Dr. Robert Wynia of Great Falls, Montana discussing Medicare and Medicaid. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/53)
    - 1986 0515 DC Representative Richard Bolling Birthday with Chris Dodd and Evie Dubrow, May 15, 1986; Max Baucus at 70th birthday celebration for former chairman of the House Rules Committee Congressman Richard Bolling, Senator Chris Dodd, and Evie DoBrow of the International Ladies Garment Workers Association. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/54)
    - 1986 0516 DC MM Former Staff Intern Jay Markley of OK, May 16, 1986; Max Baucus with former intern Jay Markley of Oklahoma and of Washington and Lee University. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/55)
    - 1986 0516 DC MM Former Staff Intern Nancy Walcot of MA, May 16, 1986; Max Baucus with former intern, Exeter student Nancy Walcott of Massachusetts. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/56)
    - 1986 0516 DC MM Former Staff Interns Steve Smith and Georgia Lambros of Missoula, May 16, 1986; Max Baucus with former interns Steve Smith of the University of Montana and Georgia Lambros, both of Missoula. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/57)
    - 1986 0516 DC MM Former Staff USFS Fellow Fred Stormer, May 16, 1986; Max Baucus with US Forest Service Congressional Fellow Fred Stormer. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/58)
    - 1986 0531 MT Helena Governors Cup, May 31, 1986; Max Baucus being interviewed after running in Montana Governor's Cup in Helena, Montana with constituent. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/59)
    - 1986 0603 DC American Alliance Fitness Assessment Day, June 3, 1986; Max Baucus at first American Alliance Congressional Fitness Assessment Day at the Dirksen Senate Office Building. (Box-folder Series 13 - 20/60)
    - 1986 0603DC MM Bill Peters of Bozeman, June 3, 1986; Max Baucus with Dr. Bill Peters of OB-GYN Associates and of Bozeman, Montana, discussing health legislation. (Box-folder Series 13 - 21/1)
    - 1986 0603 DC MM Soil Conservation Service Stakeholders, June 3, 1986; Max Baucus with USDA Montana Soil Conservation Service Award recipient Susan Tharp of Montana Soil Conservation Service and Ed Tharp, Rob Tharp, Doug and Delores Kelso, all of Manhattan, Montana. (Box-folder Series 13 - 21/2)
    - 1986 0609 DC MM Responsibility for Ending Starvation Using Legislation Results, June 9, 1986; Max Baucus with Ken Del Mastro and Deborah Cox of Billings, Montana and of RESULTS (Responsibility for Ending Starvation Using Legislation), discussing domestic hunger and anti-hunger self sufficiency bill. (Box-folder Series 13 - 21/3)